After the request returned successfully let's
بعد أن رجع الطلب بنجاح
pause inside the function to check out what's been returned.
دعنا نقف مؤقتًا داخل الدالة للتحقق من ما تم إرجاعه.
To do that let's add a debugger right here.
للقيام بذلك دعنا نضيف مصحح أخطاء هنا.
Now if I refresh the page and search for flamingos,
الآن إذا قمت بتحديث الصفحة والبحث عن طيور النحام،
it'll pause that this value is the XHR object
فإنها ستتوقف مؤقتًا، هذه القيمة هي كائن XHR نفسه
itself and the response is stored in response text.
ويتم تخزين الاستجابة في نص الاستجابة.
This is a Json response and shows all of the text.
هذه هي استجابة Json وتعرض كل النص.
We can see this information a lot more easily in the network pane.
يمكننا أن نرى هذه المعلومات بسهولة أكبر في جزء الشبكة.
This request returned 13 responses.
قام هذا الطلب بإرجاع 13 استجابة.
So we need to convert the response from Json into a JavaScript object,
لذلك نحن بحاجة إلى تحويل الاستجابة من Json إلى كائن JavaScript،
then format the data.
ثم تنسيق البيانات.
Now, to get the first image.
الآن، للحصول على الصورة الأولى.
Now that we have the first image,
الآن لدينا الصورة الأولى،
we just need to add it to the page.
نحن بحاجة فقط لإضافتها إلى الصفحة.
This code will add a figure element with an image point to the image
سيضيف هذا الكود عنصر رسم توضيحي بنقطة صورة إلى الصورة
from unsplash and a caption of the person that took the photo.
من unsplash وتسمية توضيحية من الشخص الذي أخذ الصورة.
It will add this inside the response container as the first element.
سيضيف هذا داخل حاوية الاستجابة باعتباره العنصر الأول.
Now we also want to make sure that we handle the case if no images are returned.
الآن نريد أيضًا أن نتأكد من أننا نعالج الحالة إذا لم يتم إرجاع الصور.
This will check to make sure there's some image results returned.
سيتحقق هذا للتأكد من إرجاع بعض نتائج الصور.
If there aren't any,
إذا لم يكن هناك أي نتائج،
then we'll just display a message that there are no images.
سنقوم فقط بعرض رسالة بأنه لا توجد صور.